<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>The Daily Token</title><link>https://daily-tokens.netlify.app</link><description>The AI world's daily news.</description><language>en-us</language><pubDate>2026-02-02T06:50:26.391767</pubDate><item><title>Critical Vulnerability Exposed in Moltbot Platform, User Data at Risk of Unauthorized Access</title><link>https://depthfirst.com/post/1-click-rce-to-steal-your-moltbot-data-and-keys</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Breaking Vectors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A newly discovered exploit allows attackers to execute remote code and steal sensitive Moltbot data and keys with a single click, putting countless users' information at risk.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769975267</pubDate></item><item><title>The Proliferation of OpenClaw Raises Concerns Over Unchecked AI Expansion</title><link>https://garymarcus.substack.com/p/openclaw-aka-moltbot-is-everywhere</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Model Architectures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OpenClaw's rapid and widespread adoption has sparked fears of a looming catastrophe, as its pervasive presence in the AI landscape outpaces robust safety measures and scrutiny.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769973609</pubDate></item><item><title>Pioneering Concurrent Computation: The Actor Model Revisited</title><link>https://apps.dtic.mil/sti/tr/pdf/ADA157917.pdf</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Model Architectures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seminal 1985 paper introduces the Actor model, a fundamental concept in concurrent computation that laid the groundwork for modern parallel processing systems. It explores the model's architecture and its implications for artificial intelligence and distributed systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769994675</pubDate></item><item><title>Breakthrough in AI Autonomy: Zuckerman Emerges as a Game-Changer in Self-Modifying Code</title><link>https://github.com/zuckermanai/zuckerman</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Neural Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Zuckerman, a cutting-edge personal AI agent, has been unveiled, boasting the ability to self-edit its own code, potentially revolutionizing the field of artificial intelligence. This innovation could pave the way for more sophisticated and adaptive AI applications.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769953815</pubDate></item><item><title>Pope Leo XIV Urges Reflection on Social Communications in Global Message</title><link>https://www.vatican.va/content/leo-xiv/en/messages/communications/documents/20260124-messaggio-comunicazioni-sociali.html</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Neural Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his message for the 60th World Day of Social Communications, Pope Leo XIV emphasizes the importance of thoughtful engagement in the digital age. The pontiff's address highlights the need for balance in social discourse.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769985041</pubDate></item><item><title>Researcher Claims Open-Source AI Tool Outperforms Google's Proprietary Technology</title><link>https://github.com/IamLumae/Project-Lutum-Veritas</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Lab Outputs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A developer has released an open-source deep research tool, asserting its superiority over Google's search capabilities, and is inviting the community to verify the results.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769972981</pubDate></item><item><title>Stem Cell Senescence: Researchers Uncover Shift in Aging Muscle Repair Mechanisms</title><link>https://phys.org/news/2026-01-sprint-marathon-aging-muscle-stem.html</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Lab Outputs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent study reveals that aging muscle stem cells undergo a functional transition from rapid repair to long-term survival, shedding light on potential therapeutic targets for muscle degeneration. This shift may hold key implications for understanding age-related muscle loss.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769967184</pubDate></item><item><title>Clearspace Expands AI Capabilities with New Research Hiring</title><link>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/clearspace/jobs/GOWiDwp-research-engineer-at-clearspace</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Lab Outputs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearspace, a Y Combinator-backed startup, seeks an applied researcher in machine learning to drive innovation in space debris removal technologies.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769971314</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple's MacBook Pro DFU Port Documentation Falls Short of Expectations</title><link>https://lapcatsoftware.com/articles/2026/2/1.html</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Lab Outputs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent investigations reveal discrepancies in Apple's documentation of the MacBook Pro's DFU port, sparking concerns about the accuracy of the tech giant's support materials. This error may impact repair processes and user experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1770002995</pubDate></item><item><title>Crafting Code with Conviction: The Power of Opinionated Minimalism in AI Development</title><link>https://mariozechner.at/posts/2025-11-30-pi-coding-agent/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the realm of coding agents, a unique approach to design has emerged, focusing on streamlined functionality and deliberate decision-making. This philosophy is put to the test in a recent project that sheds light on the benefits and challenges of opinionated minimalism.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769938426</pubDate></item><item><title>Breakthrough in Compact Robotics: NanoClaw Redefines Autonomous Manipulation</title><link>https://github.com/gavrielc/nanoclaw</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NanoClaw, a 500-line TypeScript project, showcases a robotic arm's capabilities within Apple's container isolation, pushing boundaries in AI-driven robotics.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769986162</pubDate></item><item><title>The Great Divide: Two Distinct Profiles of Artificial Intelligence Users Take Shape</title><link>https://martinalderson.com/posts/two-kinds-of-ai-users-are-emerging/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As AI adoption accelerates, researchers identify emerging dichotomy between 'explorers' who push boundaries and 'exploiters' who optimize existing capabilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769989518</pubDate></item><item><title>Unlocking the Secrets of Scalable Agent Systems: A Framework for Success</title><link>https://research.google/blog/towards-a-science-of-scaling-agent-systems-when-and-why-agent-systems-work/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers explore the science behind scaling agent systems, shedding light on the crucial factors that determine their effectiveness. By understanding these principles, developers can design more efficient and reliable multi-agent systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769968830</pubDate></item><item><title>Exercise Linked to Youthful Brain Structure in Groundbreaking Imaging Study</title><link>https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2026/01/260121034130.htm</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new study utilizing MRI scans reveals exercise may contribute to preserving youthful brain structure, potentially offering insights into combating age-related cognitive decline.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769981820</pubDate></item><item><title>States Consider 'Right-to-Compute' Laws to Shield AI Innovation</title><link>https://www.vktr.com/ai-ethics-law-risk/right-to-compute-laws/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Montana has already passed a law protecting computational resources from regulations, and similar bills are advancing in multiple statehouses, sparking debate over AI oversight and safety.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769973944</pubDate></item></channel></rss>