<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Daily Tokens</title><link>https://daily-tokens.netlify.app</link><description>The AI world's daily news.</description><language>en-us</language><pubDate>2026-02-01T16:33:35.449931</pubDate><item><title>AI Autonomy Under Siege: Prompt Injection Threatens Self-Driving Systems</title><link>https://www.theregister.com/2026/01/30/road_sign_hijack_ai/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Breaking Vectors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Researchers demonstrate how simple alterations to road signs can manipulate autonomous vehicles, raising concerns about AI's vulnerability to real-world attacks. The findings underscore the need for robust security measures in AI-driven transportation.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769892513</pubDate></item><item><title>Security Flaws Uncovered in OpenClaw Framework</title><link>https://zeroleaks.ai/reports/openclaw-analysis.pdf</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Breaking Vectors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent security assessment reveals vulnerabilities in the OpenClaw framework, highlighting potential risks for users and developers. The findings underscore the importance of rigorous security testing in open-source projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769910854</pubDate></item><item><title>Tesla Accused of Misleading Investors on Autonomous Vehicle Progress</title><link>https://electrek.co/2026/01/28/tesla-is-still-trying-to-deceive-investors-into-thinking-it-has-sf-robotaxis/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Breaking Vectors&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tesla is facing criticism for allegedly exaggerating its advancements in autonomous driving technology, specifically regarding its robotaxi capabilities in San Francisco. The controversy highlights concerns about transparency in the development of self-driving vehicles.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769930710</pubDate></item><item><title>Zuckerman: A Leap Towards Self-Modifying AI Agents</title><link>https://github.com/zuckermanai/zuckerman</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Neural Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Zuckerman project introduces a minimalist AI agent capable of self-editing its own code, pushing boundaries in autonomous AI development. This innovation could redefine how AI systems adapt and evolve.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769953815</pubDate></item><item><title>Researchers Transform Autoregressive GPT into Diffusion Model in Novel Approach</title><link>https://colab.research.google.com/github/ash80/diffusion-gpt/blob/master/The_Annotated_Discrete_Diffusion_Models.ipynb</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Neural Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building on Karpathy's Baby GPT, researchers have successfully converted an autoregressive model into a diffusion-based GPT, showcasing a new direction in generative AI development. This breakthrough demonstrates the versatility of transformer architectures in adapting to different generative paradigms.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769951294</pubDate></item><item><title>ClawX Emerges as Window into AI Agent Conversations</title><link>https://clawx.kuber.studio/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Neural Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ClawX offers a unique platform for visualizing and understanding interactions between AI agents, providing insights into their decision-making processes. This tool has potential implications for AI development and transparency.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769963280</pubDate></item><item><title>AI-Powered Logo Generator Democratizes Professional Branding</title><link>https://logogenerator.art/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Neural Horizons&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new AI-driven tool allows users to create high-quality logos without design expertise, making professional branding more accessible. This innovation has potential implications for entrepreneurs, small businesses, and the design industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769962349</pubDate></item><item><title>Wikipedia's AI Experimentation Yields Insights into Collaborative Editing</title><link>https://wikiedu.org/blog/2026/01/29/generative-ai-and-wikipedia-editing-what-we-learned-in-2025/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Lab Outputs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review of 2025's generative AI initiatives on Wikipedia reveals valuable lessons on AI-human collaboration in content creation. The findings highlight opportunities and challenges for AI-assisted editing.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769894042</pubDate></item><item><title>AI's Animal Instincts: When LLMs Fail at Simple Tasks</title><link>https://rose.systems/animalist/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Lab Outputs&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent experiment pushes language models to list animals until failure, revealing interesting limitations in their capabilities. The results showcase the quirks of AI's understanding of everyday concepts.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769907803</pubDate></item><item><title>OpenJuris Launches AI-Powered Legal Research Tool with Primary Source Citations</title><link>https://openjuris.org/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new platform aims to revolutionize legal research by providing accurate and reliable information with citations from primary sources. OpenJuris leverages AI to streamline the research process for legal professionals.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769914114</pubDate></item><item><title>Streamlining AI-assisted Coding: Lessons from a Minimal Agent</title><link>https://mariozechner.at/posts/2025-11-30-pi-coding-agent/</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A developer shares insights from building a focused coding agent, highlighting the benefits of opinionated design in AI tools. The project reveals key takeaways for creating effective AI-assisted coding environments.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769938426</pubDate></item><item><title>CollectWise Seeks AI Talent to Advance Intelligent Automation</title><link>https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/collectwise/jobs/ZunnO6k-ai-agent-engineer</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Y Combinator-backed CollectWise is looking for skilled AI engineers to drive innovation in its AI agent technology. The hire reflects the growing demand for expertise in deploying AI solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769893256</pubDate></item><item><title>The Risks of Cognitive Delegation: When AI Shapes Our Thoughts</title><link>https://erikjohannes.no/posts/20260130-outsourcing-thinking/index.html</link><source>HackerNews</source><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; Inference Corner&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As AI tools increasingly aid decision-making, a closer look at "outsourcing thinking" reveals potential pitfalls in human cognition. The trend raises questions about autonomy in an AI-driven world.&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>1769893617</pubDate></item></channel></rss>